dlblair.com 2014-02-13

# Privacy Policy - D.L. Blair, Inc.

Your privacy is very important to us. This privacy policy describes how D.L. Blair collects, uses and safeguards personal information gathered about you.

D.L. Blair collects information that can identify you, such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and other similar information ("Your Information") when it is voluntarily submitted. For example, you may submit Your Information while entering a contest, sweepstakes or other promotion either through a paper form or via the internet.

We may also collect other information transferred by you in connection with your visit to this site including your IP Address and other information gathered through our weblogs and "cookies." A cookie is a piece of information that our webserver sends to your computer when you access a website. Then when you come back our site will detect whether you have one of our cookies on your computer. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the site and help us analyze site usage more accurately.

We endeavor to protect Your Information using physical, electronic or procedural security measures appropriate to the sensitivity of the information in our control. These measures include safeguards to protect Your Information against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use and modification. All reasonable steps are taken to prevent unauthorized use or disclosure of Your Information.

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of Your Information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information, including transmission of information using industry standard secure socket layer encryption (SSL).

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in the following ways:

  1. To administer a contest, sweepstakes, promotion, survey or other site feature;
  2. To notify you of a potential prize which you may have won in a promotion or to respond to an email,  
     request, or other type of inquiry;
  3. To personalize your experience helping us better respond to your individual needs.

D.L. Blair will retain Your Information only for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected.

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under age 13 online, without parental permission. Children under the age of 13 are required to have permission from a parent or guardian before submitting personal information online.

It is our policy to never sell, trade, or provide any information, including mailing lists, to anyone else with the exception of trusted third parties who assist us in conducting our business or servicing you and our clients and their agencies (where applicable).

_Notice to California Residents_  
Under California's "Shine the Light" law, California residents who provide personal information in obtaining products or services for personal, family or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us once per calendar year information about the customer information we shared, if any, with third parties for their direct marketing purposes, including the categories of information and names and addresses of third parties with whom we shared the information. As stated above, it is our policy to never sell, trade, or provide any information, including mailing lists, to anyone else with the exception of trusted third parties who assist us in conducting our business or servicing you and our clients and their agencies (where applicable).

To request this information from D.L. Blair, California residents may email the Privacy Officer at _Privacyofficer@dlblair.com_ or write to us at the address listed below and reference "California Privacy Rights" in your request. Please note that not all information sharing is covered by the "Shine the Light" law, and we will only include in our response information relating to our sharing practices for covered information.

_Contact Information_  
If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact the Privacy Officer:

Privacy Officer c/o D.L. Blair, Inc.  
1548 Front St  
Blair, NE 68008  
Phone: 402-426-4701  
Fax: 402-426-4706  
Email: _Privacyofficer@dlblair.com_

As a convenience to our visitors, this Website currently contains links to a number of sites that we believe may offer useful information. The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to those sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy, security, data collection, and distribution policies.

D.L. Blair will update this Privacy Policy occasionally. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will also revise the "Last Updated" date below on the Privacy Policy. D.L. Blair encourages you to review this Privacy Policy periodically to be informed of how we are protecting your information and to be aware of any changes to the Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the site after the posting of any amended Privacy Policy shall constitute your agreement to be bound by any such changes. Any changes to this Privacy Policy are effective immediately after being posted by D.L. Blair.

Last Updated: 5/8/13
